<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinder Skullz Abyss Feed</title>
    <link>https://sinder-skullz-rss-feed.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Chaotic sermons and metal news reborn in the flames of the Skullz cult.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
        <item>
            <title>⚡☠ AL PITRELLI RECALLS ALMOST JOINING OZZY OSBOURNE’S BAND AS JAKE E. LEE'S REPLACEMENT ☠⚡</title>
            <link>https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54764787233_376b42bc54_b.jpg</link>
            <description>**Title: AL PITRELLI Almost Shredded for OZZY OSBOURNE - A Heavy Metal Saga! 🤘💀**

**Summary: Hell yeah, metalheads! Picture this: a shadowy realm of heavy riffs and screaming guitars, where fates collide in the chaos of rock ‘n’ roll glory! The legendary Al Pitrelli, a true titan of the strings, recently unleashed a wicked tale while howlin’ with the dudes at Radio Forrest 96.9 The Eagle. This isn’t just some soft ballad, folks—this is the stuff of myths!**

**Picture it: the chance to step into the boots of the ultimate axe-slinger Jake E. Lee in the realm of OZZY OSBOURNE! 🦇🔥 Pitrelli felt the thunder rumble through his veins, a siren call from the Prince of Darkness himself! Imagine the all-out sonic warfare—the shriek of distorted solos, the pounding of the drums like a thousand war drums echoing from the depths of rock hell! But sometimes, the fates play cruel tricks in the metallic realm!**

**Diving deep into the abyss, we discover that this near-miss is just as electrifying as the screams of the night! Al's saga serves as a brutal reminder that every riff, every moment, could change the course of heavy metal history. He may have dodged the dark wizard's call, but the spirit of metal runs through his veins—fueling the fire of his epic journey with Savatage and beyond! 🤘💰💀**

**So, raise your horns and drown in the glorious chaos of what could have been! We’re all about those almosts, the near-hits, the thrashing vibrations that keep us electrified! For the complete, spine-tingling tale, check it out at Metal Injection! Until the next riff, stay wild, my crypto and metal beasts!**

#MetalCulture #ThrashMetal #DeathMetal #MetalScene #HeavyMetal</description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[**Title: AL PITRELLI Almost Shredded for OZZY OSBOURNE - A Heavy Metal Saga! 🤘💀**

**Summary: Hell yeah, metalheads! Picture this: a shadowy realm of heavy riffs and screaming guitars, where fates collide in the chaos of rock ‘n’ roll glory! The legendary Al Pitrelli, a true titan of the strings, recently unleashed a wicked tale while howlin’ with the dudes at Radio Forrest 96.9 The Eagle. This isn’t just some soft ballad, folks—this is the stuff of myths!**

**Picture it: the chance to step into the boots of the ultimate axe-slinger Jake E. Lee in the realm of OZZY OSBOURNE! 🦇🔥 Pitrelli felt the thunder rumble through his veins, a siren call from the Prince of Darkness himself! Imagine the all-out sonic warfare—the shriek of distorted solos, the pounding of the drums like a thousand war drums echoing from the depths of rock hell! But sometimes, the fates play cruel tricks in the metallic realm!**

**Diving deep into the abyss, we discover that this near-miss is just as electrifying as the screams of the night! Al's saga serves as a brutal reminder that every riff, every moment, could change the course of heavy metal history. He may have dodged the dark wizard's call, but the spirit of metal runs through his veins—fueling the fire of his epic journey with Savatage and beyond! 🤘💰💀**

**So, raise your horns and drown in the glorious chaos of what could have been! We’re all about those almosts, the near-hits, the thrashing vibrations that keep us electrified! For the complete, spine-tingling tale, check it out at Metal Injection! Until the next riff, stay wild, my crypto and metal beasts!**

#MetalCulture #ThrashMetal #DeathMetal #MetalScene #HeavyMetal]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54764787233_376b42bc54_b.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>