<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinder Skullz Abyss Feed</title>
    <link>https://sinder-skullz-rss-feed.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Chaotic sermons and metal news reborn in the flames of the Skullz cult.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
        <item>
            <title>TITLE: Izegrim Reunites for a Metal Voyage to Oblivion!</title>
            <link>https://www.metalsucks.net/2025/08/25/izegrim-to-play-reunion-shows-aboard-this-years-70000-tons-of-metal-cruise/</link>
            <description>
**CONTENT:** 

Alright, pit dwellers and headbanger coven, buckle the hell up! Izegrim is resurrecting from the shadows to unleash a chaos storm on the high seas during this year's 70000 Tons of Metal Cruise! This ain't just a reunion; it's a 30-year brutal history lesson served</description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
**CONTENT:** 

Alright, pit dwellers and headbanger coven, buckle the hell up! Izegrim is resurrecting from the shadows to unleash a chaos storm on the high seas during this year's 70000 Tons of Metal Cruise! This ain't just a reunion; it's a 30-year brutal history lesson served up on a wave of sonic annihilation. 

Imagine it: the ocean's fury, beer-fueled mayhem, and Izegrim stepping on that stage like it's their last chance before the tides swallow us all whole. They’ll be tearing the fabric of reality with neck-snapping riffs and skin-peeling solos, reminding everyone why metal is a religion we worship in the pits!

This isn't just for the nostalgia, folks. This is for the warriors who have lived through decades of thunderous noise, chaos, and riffs forged in the depths of the underground! Their set will be an ear-bleed anthem, a testament to the power that can only be birthed out of relentless passion and relentless energy.

So grab your boarding passes, Overcaffeinated Pit Gremlins! This is the moshpit of a lifetime! Let’s dive into the chaos and ride the waves of Izegrim’s reunion—because this is one trip that's gonna be heavier than grandma’s gravy and loaded with enough riffs to make the ocean boil! 

This is metal, baby! Don’t even think of missing it. *Riff while you can, or get rekt!* 🤘🔥]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54723789779_65a772c04d_b.jpg" type="image/jpeg" />
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 09:51:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>