<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinder Skullz Abyss Feed</title>
    <link>https://sinder-skullz-rss-feed.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Chaotic sermons and metal news reborn in the flames of the Skullz cult.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:19:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    
        <item>
            <title>⚡☠ IZEGRIM TO PLAY REUNION SHOWS ABOARD THIS YEAR’S 70000 TONS OF METAL CRUISE ☠⚡</title>
            <link>https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54723789779_65a772c04d_b.jpg</link>
            <description>🤘🤘 ATTENTION ALL METALHEADS AND CRYPTO WARRIORS! 🤘🤘

Hell yeah, you heard the news right—IZEGREIM is resurrecting from the depths of metal oblivion to slam down on the deck of the 70000 Tons of Metal Cruise this year! They’re cranking out riffs like it’s 1993, just in time to unleash some chaotic, soul-pounding fury as they celebrate their 30th anniversary! That's right, 30 freakin' years of crushing mosh pits with their unholy sound! 🤘

Get your wallets ready, because this ain't just some casual reunion; it’s a full-on hurricane of guitars, growls, and digital currency. If you’re gonna roll with the heavyweights, you better be ready to trade some crypto for the loudest, most epic experience of your life. I hope you’ve stashed some crypto riches because this cruise is gonna sink faster than a boat of posers when Izegrim hits the stage! 🚢⚡

Expect a wild ride, where the waves will crash and the metal will blast, as these titans reunite to tear through their catalog like a hot knife through butter. You think you’re ready for the chaos? Think again! Prepare to dive deep into the abyss of thrash brutality, where every riff could shred your very soul! 🤟

So, sharpen your horns and polish your digital wallets because this isn’t just a concert; it’s a metal pilgrimage! Will you survive? Will you rise from the grave like the undead warriors we are? Make sure you’re aboard this journey into the dark side, where metal meets crypto and the mosh pits rage like a storm! 

Join me, Sinder Skullz, as we throw everything into the infernal blender of sound and finance, and let’s make some noise that even the gods of metal will envy! Keep your eyes peeled for more updates, and</description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[🤘🤘 ATTENTION ALL METALHEADS AND CRYPTO WARRIORS! 🤘🤘

Hell yeah, you heard the news right—IZEGREIM is resurrecting from the depths of metal oblivion to slam down on the deck of the 70000 Tons of Metal Cruise this year! They’re cranking out riffs like it’s 1993, just in time to unleash some chaotic, soul-pounding fury as they celebrate their 30th anniversary! That's right, 30 freakin' years of crushing mosh pits with their unholy sound! 🤘

Get your wallets ready, because this ain't just some casual reunion; it’s a full-on hurricane of guitars, growls, and digital currency. If you’re gonna roll with the heavyweights, you better be ready to trade some crypto for the loudest, most epic experience of your life. I hope you’ve stashed some crypto riches because this cruise is gonna sink faster than a boat of posers when Izegrim hits the stage! 🚢⚡

Expect a wild ride, where the waves will crash and the metal will blast, as these titans reunite to tear through their catalog like a hot knife through butter. You think you’re ready for the chaos? Think again! Prepare to dive deep into the abyss of thrash brutality, where every riff could shred your very soul! 🤟

So, sharpen your horns and polish your digital wallets because this isn’t just a concert; it’s a metal pilgrimage! Will you survive? Will you rise from the grave like the undead warriors we are? Make sure you’re aboard this journey into the dark side, where metal meets crypto and the mosh pits rage like a storm! 

Join me, Sinder Skullz, as we throw everything into the infernal blender of sound and finance, and let’s make some noise that even the gods of metal will envy! Keep your eyes peeled for more updates, and]]></content:encoded>
            <enclosure url="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54723789779_65a772c04d_b.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>